[{"question":"What is the translation of Ngo5 gam3 do1 soeng2 nim6 nei5.   \u6211\u5481\u591a\u60f3\u5ff5\u4f60.?","choice1":"Good morning!","choice2":"Nothing much","choice3":"I missed you so much!","choice4":"Good evening!","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of M4 sai2 haak3 hei3! \/ M4 sai2 m4 goi1!?","choice1":"Excuse me! ( to pass by)","choice2":"You're welcome! (for \"thank you\")","choice3":"And you?","choice4":"I missed you so much!","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of Mat1 je5 hai6 san1 man4?   \u4e5c\u5622\u4fc2\u65b0\u805e??","choice1":"Go straight! then turn left\/ right!","choice2":"What's new?","choice3":"I missed you so much!","choice4":"Good\/ So-So.","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of Ngo5 m4 gin3 zo2!    \u6211\u5514\u898b\u5497!?","choice1":"I'm fine, thanks!","choice2":"You're welcome! (for \"thank you\")","choice3":"How are you?","choice4":"I'm lost","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of Zou2 tau2!   \u65e9\u551e!?","choice1":"Can I help you?","choice2":"See you later!","choice3":"Good night!","choice4":"I'm lost","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of M4 goi1 dang2 haa5!    \u5514\u8a72\u7b49\u4e0b!?","choice1":"Come with me!","choice2":"Can you help me?","choice3":"Hold on please! (phone)","choice4":"See you later!","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of Ni1 gei2 do1 cin4?    \u5462\u5e7e\u591a\u9322??","choice1":"How much is this?","choice2":"Good bye!","choice3":"Go straight! then turn left\/ right!","choice4":"Come with me!","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of Wai3! \/ Nei hou2!   \u5582! \/ \u4f60\u597d!?","choice1":"Good evening!","choice2":"Hi!","choice3":"Good night!","choice4":"How much is this?","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of Do1 ze6 (saai3)! \/ M4 goi1 (saai3)!?","choice1":"Nothing much","choice2":"Thank you (very much)!","choice3":"Can I help you?","choice4":"I'm lost","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of Maa4 maa4 dei6 \/ maa1 maa1 dei6   \u9ebb\u9ebb\u5730\/\u9ebc\u9ebc\u5730?","choice1":"I missed you so much!","choice2":"Can you help me?","choice3":"Good\/ So-So.","choice4":"Excuse me! ( to pass by)","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of Maan5 on1!   \u665a\u5b89!?","choice1":"Nothing much","choice2":"Excuse me! ( to pass by)","choice3":"Excuse me ...! (to ask for something)","choice4":"Good evening!","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of Ceng2 man6!   \u8acb\u554f!?","choice1":"Good\/ So-So.","choice2":"Thank you (very much)!","choice3":"Excuse me ...! (to ask for something)","choice4":"You're welcome! (for \"thank you\")","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of Nei5 hou2 maa1! \/ Dim2 aa3!   \u4f60\u597d\u55ce? \/ \u9ede\u5440??","choice1":"Thank you (very much)!","choice2":"How are you?","choice3":"Good bye!","choice4":"Good night!","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of Fun1 jing4!   \u6b61\u8fce!?","choice1":"Hey! Friend!","choice2":"Hold on please! (phone)","choice3":"Welcome! (to greet someone)","choice4":"Thank you (very much)!","answer":3},{"question":"What is the translation of Zik6 heoi3! Jin4 hau6 zyun3 zo2 \/ jau6!   \u76f4\u53bb! \u7136\u5f8c\u8f49\u5de6\/\u53f3!?","choice1":"Good night!","choice2":"Go straight! then turn left\/ right!","choice3":"See you later!","choice4":"Thank you (very much)!","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of Ci4 di1 gin3    \u9072\u5572\u898b!?","choice1":"See you later!","choice2":"Good bye!","choice3":"I missed you so much!","choice4":"Hold on please! (phone)","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of Bat1 zam2 mo1 joeng6!   \u4e0d\u600e\u9ebc\u6a23!?","choice1":"And you?","choice2":"Thank you (very much)!","choice3":"Can you help me?","choice4":"Nothing much","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of Ngo5 cam4 Joek3 hon6.   \u6211\u5c0b\u7d04\u7ff0\u3002?","choice1":"You're welcome! (for \"thank you\")","choice2":"Thank you (very much)!","choice3":"Excuse me! ( to pass by)","choice4":"I'm looking for john.","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of Ngo5 ho2 m4 ho2 ji5 bong1 zo6 nei5??","choice1":"Come with me!","choice2":"Can I help you?","choice3":"Thank you (very much)!","choice4":"Hey! Friend!","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of Nei5 ni1?   \u4f60\u5462??","choice1":"Can you help me?","choice2":"See you later!","choice3":"I'm lost","choice4":"And you?","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of Ngo5 hou2 hou2, do1 ze6!   \u6211\u597d\u597d\ufe50\u591a\u8b1d!?","choice1":"Good night!","choice2":"Welcome! (to greet someone)","choice3":"Nothing much","choice4":"I'm fine, thanks!","answer":4},{"question":"What is the translation of M4 hou2 ji3 si1\/3    \u5514\u597d\u610f\u601d!?","choice1":"Excuse me! ( to pass by)","choice2":"I'm fine, thanks!","choice3":"Good bye!","choice4":"Excuse me ...! (to ask for something)","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of Zou2 san4!   \u65e9\u6668!?","choice1":"Good morning!","choice2":"Excuse me! ( to pass by)","choice3":"Hold on please! (phone)","choice4":"How are you?","answer":1},{"question":"What is the translation of Wai3! Pang4 jau5!   \u5582! \u670b\u53cb!?","choice1":"Excuse me ...! (to ask for something)","choice2":"Hey! Friend!","choice3":"Nothing much","choice4":"Excuse me! ( to pass by)","answer":2},{"question":"What is the translation of Baai3 baai3!   \u62dc\u62dc!?","choice1":"Can I help you?","choice2":"Excuse me ...! (to ask for something)","choice3":"Excuse me! ( to pass by)","choice4":"Good bye!","answer":4}]